<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- App title-->
    <string name="app_name">M.S.Giusto Tourist Official</string>
    <!-- MONUMENTS -->
    <string name="telusiano_title">saint mary in telusiano</string>
    <string name="telusiano_address">Tolomei St</string>
    <string name="telusiano_schedule">Closed for work</string>
    <string name="telusiano_description">The church was restored between 1513 and 1529 at the behest of Nicolò Bonafede from Monte San Giusto (1464–1534), an important figure of the Papal court and Bishop of Chiusi, to be his family\'s mausoleum. The exterior of the church is in simple brick except for the portal in travertine holding the Bishop\'s coat–of–arms and the inscriptions “S. MARIA DE PIETATE” (Saint Mary of the Pietà) and along the lintel: “N [icolaus].BO[na]FIDES EPISCOPVS CLUSINUS FVNDITVS RESTAVRAVIT” (Niccolò Bishop of Chiusi restored [it] from its foundations). Inside the church there is a masterpiece of the Venetian painter Lorenzo Lotto, his Crucifixion (c.1529–30) still in its original frame, which itself is an outstanding example of Renaissance woodwork. In this painting, Niccolò Bonafede is shown kneeling and contemplating Mary as she faints. Of considerable interest are also the remains of late 16th-century frescoes attributed to one of Lotto\'s students, Durante Nobili di Caldarola, a copy of the Madonna of Trapani by Nino Pisano (late 17th-century); and a 15th-century Vesperbild (or Pietà), which is the only remaining visible link to the Medieval church.</string>
    <string name="bonafede_title">bonafede palace</string>
    <string name="bonafede_schedule">Open every day</string>
    <string name="bonafede_address">Garibaldi Sq.</string>
    <string name="bonafede_description">Built as a patrician residence for Nicolò Bonafede, Bishop of Chiusi, Palazzo Bonafede is one of the greatest examples of Renaissance architecture in the Marche region, together with the Ducal Palace in Urbino. It was designed to honour Bonafede, exalting him in his hometown, and for his role as mercenary and for his political and military responsibilities, tributes of which can be read in the many inscriptions on the palace\'s facade. The Guelf windows decorated with the monogram of the Bishop, the frieze with inscription (1513) and the portal in Istrian stone that celebrate Bonafede\'s victory over the Malatesta family of Rimini, sculpted by Pesimonti (1524) from Ancona, are particularly noteworthy. Of great interest inside, as well as the Renaissance courtyard, are the so–called \"camera picta\" (also called the Bishop\'s Room) on the ground floor, and, on the first and \"noble\" floor the band of frescoes depicting Nicolò Bonafede\'s Triumphs, fragments of a larger decoration from 1515–1520 attributed to the Spanish painter Johannes Hispanus. In the council room there is a painting by Luigi Fontana, from 1869, that depicts Niccolò Bonafede looking over the design for his palace.</string>
    <string name="museo_address">Bonafede St.</string>
    <string name="museo_schedule">Open every day</string>
    <string name="museo_title">Museum pole</string>
    <string name="museo_description">The partly underground floor of the Palazzo Bonafede, originally used by the family as kitchens, food storage, cellar and olive oil presses, today hosts Monte San Giusto\'s Museum. Since 2013 the Museum has housed the municipal collections, which comprise three distinct parts:</string>
    <string name="porte_address">Circonvallazione St.</string>
    <string name="porte_schedule">Opening hours: always visible</string>
    <string name="porte_description">The gate faces north and preserves many characteristics of its original appearance as Torre Portaia (that is, a tower placed to protect the gate). Its barrel vault with a double portcullis dates it to around 1390. Over the centuries the gate has undergone many modifications, such as the destruction of its crenellated cornice.</string>
    <string name="porte_title">door to the hall</string>
    <string name="priori_title">priori palace</string>
    <string name="priori_schedule">Always open</string>
    <string name="priori_address">Aldo More Sq.</string>
    <string name="priori_description">Built between 1763 and 1770 on the place of the former Medieval Palazzo Priorale, Palazzo dei Priori is the work of the Lombard architect Giovanni Battista Vassalli, adopted son of Monte San Giusto and responsible also for the restoration of the Collegiate Church. Palazzo dei Priori hosted the town hall until shortly after WWII when it was moved to Palazzo Bonafede.</string>
    <!-- EVENTS -->
    <string name="carnival_title">carnival</string>
    <string name="clown_title">Clown&amp;Clown Festival</string>
    <string name="tammuria_title">tammuria</string>
    <string name="spring_festival_title">spring festival</string>
    <string name="carnival_description">Each year, on the Carnival Day, the streets of Monte San Giusto are filled with children and adults, on a wonderful day of party in colors, masks and wagons.</string>
    <string name="carnival_address">Macerata St.</string>
    <string name="carnival_schedule">Friday 18 February 2018, 3pm</string>
    <string name="clown_description">By the age of 12, from the last Sunday of September to the first Sunday in October, Monte San Giusto staged its "Clown&amp;Clown Festival". An international festival devoted to the clown figure in all its aspects, including the social one. The festival from which the construction of the City of Smile starts.</string>
    <string name="clown_address">all over the town</string>
    <string name="clown_schedule">21 – 28 Setptember 2018</string>
    <string name="spring_festival_schedule">18 – 21 June 2018</string>
    <string name="spring_festival_address">Garibaldi Sq.</string>
    <string name="spring_festival_description">\"Spring does not knock\", arrived at the third edition, is an occasion to celebrate the awakening of nature on the notes of the Italian songwriter. From the words of \"A Chemist\" by Fabrizio De Andrè, a song featured in his album \"Not Money Not to Love or to Heaven\" and taken from Edward Lee Masters\'s Spoon River Anthology, takes the name of the Review. To merge these two souls of the event, the historic center of Monte San Giusto will flourish, Piazza Aldo Moro will be invaded by: trees, urban gardens and a green mantle that will transform this meeting and socializing place into a garden for a few days.</string>
    <string name="tammuria_description">Back again this year the Salento Music Festival in the City of Smile. Born in 2008 thanks to the strong commitment of Rossano Romagnoli with the collaboration of Maurizio Nicolì, it offers sounds, rhythms and flavors typical of Salento that join in two evenings that attract tourists and fans to Monte San Giusto. Appointment to Friday 29 and Saturday 30 July.</string>
    <string name="tammuria_schedule">29 – 30 July 2018</string>
    <string name="tammuria_address">Garibaldi\'s Square</string>
    <string name="teatrando_title">Teatrando</string>
    <string name="teatrando_description">This year also the appointment with the show of comedy theater in the City of Sorriso by the Mabò Band and with the patronage of the City of Monte San Giusto is renewed. Here are the evenings planned, which will be accompanied by three Sundays (January 29, February 19 and March 12) of \"Families at Theater\", the event dedicated to families and, above all, to children.</string>
    <string name="teatrando_address">municipal theater</string>
    <string name="teatrando_schedule">29 January, 19 February, 12 March 2018</string>
    <!-- HOTELS RESTAURANTS -->
    <string name="rosa_title">Restaurant La Rosa dei Venti</string>
    <string name="rosa_schedule">closing day: Monday</string>
    <string name="rosa_description">The \"La Rosa dei Venti\" restaurant-pizzeria is an excellent expression of a family-run establishment. All our work of experience and passion is designed to satisfy the expectations of a clientele that is selected and careful in search of warmth, a welcome that enhances the traditions and the ancient flavors of our land. The restaurant is always available for dinners, banquets and custom made delicious and sought-after fresh fish dishes. Do not miss the imaginative \"salad\" and the fantastic \"unique dishes\" made by skilled chefs to the constant search for fresh and innovative dishes that modern gastronomic trends require. Every evening you can enjoy 100 different pizzas between desserts and salads to satisfy even the most demanding palates.</string>
    <string name="rosa_address">77 Macerata St.\n62015 Monte San Giusto (MC)\nPh. (+39) 0733–530500\nFax. (+39) 0733–530477\ninfo@hotellarosadeiventi.com</string>
    <string name="country_title">restaurant country giusto</string>
    <string name="country_schedule">always open</string>
    <string name="country_description">Country Giusto is the dream come true of its owner: to restore his family’s old house in the countryside where he spent the most beautiful moments of his childhood and  to share his memories with others. That is where his project started: the creation of a holiday home, so that his guests could benefit from its beauty, peacefulness and from the breathtaking view. The name “Country Giusto” refers firstly to the town in which the house is located (Monte San Giusto) and also to the fact of being located in the right position (the word “giusto” in Italian means “right”): the house is tucked away among the gently rolling hills typical of Le Marche, enjoying the view of distant mountains and within walking distance from the medieval hill-top town of Monte San Giusto.The Marche region is an ideal place to spend holidays, it is a concentrate of the different aspects of Italy. Countryside, mountains, sea, art, history, gastronomy and fashion: a unique and extraordinary setting that deserves to be discovered, along with the natural friendliness of its people.</string>
    <string name="country_address">38 San Giacomo St.\nMonte San Giusto (MC)\nTel. +39 3282197731\nP.IVA 01639540432\ninfo@countrygiusto.com</string>
    <string name="noceto_title">the noceto</string>
    <string name="noceto_schedule">always open</string>
    <string name="noceto_address">28 Fonte Ancona St.\n62015 - Monte San Giusto Macerata - Italy\nC.F./P.Iva: 01121460438\nPhone: (+39) 0733/53274\nMob. +39 329.6086075\nWhatsapp +39 392.2236281\ninfo@agriturismoilnoceto.com</string>
    <string name="noceto_description">The Il Noceto farmhouse is located in Monte San Giusto, a famous shoemaking town that houses a shingle by the painter Lorenzo Lotto. The property is set on a farm of about nine hectares, surrounded by greenery, surrounded by a park of walnuts, hazelnuts, ash, limes, sea and hawthorn hedges and surrounded by a small creek. For those who stay there is a pleasant breeze of well-being and tranquility, which regenerates the spirit. The scents of nature, together with the sovereign silence, make the place entirely exclusive. The recently restored farmhouse has retained the typical characteristics of the Marche country house. \"Il Noceto\" offers the overnight and breakfast service; It has spacious and comfortable en suite rooms, typical furnishings, grandmother\'s linens, in-room TVs. It is equipped with a cozy dining room with fireplace for breakfast and an outdoor wood oven. Guests can enjoy a large garden and a grove, take walks immersed in nature\'s greenery. The geographical position of the farm \"Il Noceto\" makes it an ideal point to organize tourist or business itineraries, the proximity to the comfortable expressway (ss77) allows easy connection from the Adriatic Riviera to the Sibillini Mountains, crossing art cities, lakes , ancient Abbeys, sanctuaries and suggestive resorts. Guests will find information material for cultural and gastronomic itineraries and to visit the many shoemakers in the area.</string>
    <string name="nicoli_title">Nicolì Tavern</string>
    <string name="nicoli_address">208 Circonvallazione St.</string>
    <string name="nicoli_description">-  The Exhibition Room.</string>
    <string name="nicoli_schedule">Closing day: Thursday afternoon</string>
    <string name="baiocco_address">194 Circonvallazione St. 62015 Monte San Giusti (MC) Ph. (+39) 0733 539717 Fax. (+39) 0733–530477</string>
    <string name="baiocco_description">At Ottica Baiocco you will find a wide range of eyeglasses and sunglasses from the best brands, trendy, classic and modern eyewear; we perform optometric examinations, with which to evaluate the efficiency of your vision and eventually provide you with the right prescription lenses and contact lenses to correct visual defects. Highly qualified and experienced staff, waiting for you to provide all the necessary advice in choosing the right eyewear for your needs. If you are looking for a pair of glasses or a particular frame, come from Ottica Baiocco, we have sunglasses and eyeglasses of the best brands. Come and find out more about the range of products available.</string>
    <string name="baiocco_schedule">Monday closed</string>
    <string name="baiocco_title">ottica baiocco</string>
    <string name="ciampechini_address">Corso della costituzione, 18 62015 Monte San Giusto (MC) Tel. (+39) 0733 53967</string>
    <string name="ciampechini_description">Creativity, craftsmanship and originality are the elements that make up the DNA of the Ciampechini jewelry, a symbol of the passion for the art of jewelry for three generations of the family. All the jewels, made entirely by hand and with the utmost attention to detail, are real masterpieces of goldsmith art, expression of a tradition and attention to the design of the jewel that has always characterized the exclusive and luxurious collections of jewelry Damiani. The jewels of the Damiani collections are all unique and exclusive creations, able to combine the charm of Italian jewelery with the unmistakable taste of Ciampechini, always modern and modern. From the gold ring to the elegant solitaire with diamond, from the jewel with precious stones to the timeless watch, the world of Ciampechini jewelry is always able to give an unforgettable emotion.</string>
    <string name="ciampechini_schedule">Monday closed</string>
    <string name="ciampechini_title">Ciampechini jewelry</string>
    <string name="event_tab">events</string>
    <string name="hotel_restaurants_tab">hotels and restaunrants</string>
    <string name="joelle_address">14 Monti Sala St., 14 62015 Monte San Giusto (MC) Ph. (+39) 0733 531257</string>
    <string name="joelle_description">Fiorella and Riccardo have been rated for over 20 years for their experience, quality and customer service. The whole team is always looking for new styles and the latest trends, to better satisfy its customers. London, Barcelona, Milan are for us usual destinations to carry out advanced courses on future trends. We have established multiple situations with the world of entertainment and fashion. In our salon you will be able to find the exclusive method of coloring Wella\'s Inspire hair with endless combinations; the SP Sistem Professional system, for hair care, as well as the innovative hair straightening technique. The appointment is recommended to offer a better service to customers. To find out, come and visit us and you will discover everything we can do for you.</string>
    <string name="joelle_schedule">Monday closed</string>
    <string name="joelle_title">hairdressing</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn more…</string>
    <string name="places_tab">places</string>
    <string name="rondinella_address">14 Bore Chienti St., 62015 Monte San Giusto (MC) Ph. (+39) 0733 1840417 Fax. (+39) 0733 53521</string>
    <string name="rondinella_description">The story of Rondinella begins in 1936, in the first laboratory of Alfredo and Lola Romagnoli. Their shoes are immediately appreciated for their quality and style. However, customers must go and look for them, especially in the nearby villages of Monte San Giusto. Many kilometers by bike, to receive some money and some food from the sale. In 1937 Franco was born. An only child, to whom the father does not recommend to be a shoemaker because, even if it is a beautiful profession, \"he takes your whole life; better school \". But Franco likes that profession. As a child it was a game, then at twelve it became a job, which he learned under the guidance of his grandfather. The laboratory needs space. In 1972 Franco and his wife Pina opened a small company. The shoes are signed Romagnoli Rondinella. In 2004 the current headquarters are inaugurated. The company is managed by Franco and his sons Alfredo and Alfio Romagnoli. The name of footwear today is Rondinella, a high quality brand.</string>
    <string name="rondinella_schedule">From Monday to Friday, 9am - 8pm</string>
    <string name="rondinella_title">rondinella shoes</string>
    <string name="shopping_tab">shopping</string>
    <string name="torresi_address">Piazzale Mazzini 7 62015 Monte San Giusto (MC) Ph. (+39) 0733 865467</string>
    <string name="torresi_description">Winter 2018 is rich in color and desire to live, for this reason French-Co has decided to offer a truly versatile and versatile range of women\'s clothing, suitable for any occasion! Many clothes: you can choose from a wide range of products; from tank tops to t-shirts, from cardigans to sweatshirts, there\'s everything you need to renew your wardrobe and always be in the latest fashion. In the women\'s collection, for example, you can find nylon bomber jackets or synthetic leather jackets, but also long jeans in light, medium or dark washings, and dresses and miniskirts to get the right look throughout the day. tastes, and offers a wide selection of garments always attentive to the line and new trends. French-Co thinks of everything, offering a wide range of accessories, such as colored pashminas, belts and bags, to always have the right part for your special occasions. Among the clothes you will also find the comfortable sweatshirts, and a wide choice of trousers, but also skirts and dresses to always have a trendy and young look. At French-Co you will find the right and economical garment that is right for you.</string>
    <string name="torresi_schedule">Monday closed</string>
    <string name="torresi_title">french-co di alessandra torresi</string>
    <string name="content_location_icon">location</string>
    <string name="content_location_schedule">schedule</string>
    <string name="image_of">image of %s</string>
</resources>